PERSONAL DETAILS - Muluken Getachew Amdie

Age: 24

+251939020570

mulukenrock@gmail.com
Addis Ababa, Ethiopia

Nationality: Ethiopian

Proposed Position: Full-stack Developer

From: 11/2018 **To**: Till today

Other Training: Entrepreneurship training

SUMMARY

Software development professional with 3 years, 6 months of skilled experience focusing on front-end design and development, database design and back-end design and development. Additional experience has been gained in the areas of deployment and post-deployment management of applications.

CAREER OBJECTIVE

To know more about my career and develop a much more efficient software that could improve and/or change people's life!

EDUCATION HISTORY

June 2019

Graduated from Addis Ababa Science and Technology University, College of Electrical and Mechanical Engineer ing. **B.Sc.** In Software Engineering with cgpa **3.75**

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full-stack Developer

Epsilon Technologies (2018 - 2020)

Full-stack Developer

Minab Tech and HahuJobs(2019 - 2021)

Senior Full-stack Developer

Orbit Health Services (2021 - now)

PROJECTS

☐ (2018) Developed the **EM-TYPER**, an amharic, tigrigna, oromigna and somaligna and english typing tutor software, together with a colleague ☐ (2019) Developed and implemented a product called **Tazajobs** that has both Web and mobile apps to make the life of both job seekers and employers easier. Employers can use the web app to post jobs and recruit job applicants while employees use the mobile app to find targeted jobs and apply for a job. The system was developed in vue.is, nodels, loopback, flutter, and mongodb. ☐ (2019) Developed and implemented several components of the cloudbased hahujobs net enterprise services including the attendance, leave and payroll management services. \square (2020) Developed and implemented **M4CD** a web-app that provides a variety of resources to assist Ethiopian students and alumni with career exploration and guidance, job and internship search as well as scholarships. Training and learning materials are accessible in various formats, such as images, videos, audios and text. ☐ (2021) Developed and implemented the backend and assisted admin deployment of the hahujobs's National Recruitment Platform (NRP) web-app - a platform for both local and overseas jobs seekers to register and take automated assessments for digital workforce mapping, screening as well as job placement. Features include conducting interviews, assessments, job orders and allocations. □ (2021) Developed a responsive web-app Habesha Entrepreneurs credit and saving Association (SACCO), which is available at https://habeshaentreprenurssacco.com \sqcap (2021) Developed and implemented the backend and frontend of **ohcore-health** 2.0 which is a versatile web app that allows healthcare centers and hospitals manage and digitize most of their health-care

SKILLS AND PERSONAL COMPETENCIES

Programming Skills:

work-flow.

- Development with Javascript (Express.js, NodeJS, Vue.js, NuxtJs)
- Database Design (PostgreSQL, MongoDB)
- Hasura
- Graphql
- Development with flutter
- Docker

Language Skills:

- Amharic Native Speaker
- English Fluent